

Contact



0404 652 859



wolfgang.stueckle@gmail..com



Aspendale Gardens VIC 3195



Portfolio Page



Github



<u>Linkedin</u>

Key Skills

- C/C++
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- JavaScript
- React
- Node/Express
- Flask/SQL

Non Technical Skills

- Software project management
- Leading and training of apprentices
- Raising my 2 children as a single dad
- Time management

Wolfgang Stueckle

Software Engineer

I am a seasoned professional with a strong background in software development, project management, and electrical engineering. I have a decade of experience as a business owner at Wolf Electrical, where I managed various projects, including solar PV systems installation and training apprentices. Prior to that, I held engineering roles at Robert Bosch in both Germany and Australia, where he developed software for engine control systems and worked on production issues. My educational background includes a BSc in Electrical and Electronics Engineering, a Nanodegree in C/C++ from Udacity, and a higher education diploma in Information Technology from the Academy of Information Technology/Coder Academy. In the future I would like to further develop my skills in embedded systems programming and Al.

Experience

O 2012 - 2022

Wolf Electrical

Business Owner

- Planning and installation of solar PV systems
- Underground wiring and group metering
- Completion of several new builds, multi units and private houses in required timeline
- Shop and office fit outs
- Home entertainment, data cabling, smart wiring
- Fault finding, debugging of control circuits
- Trained 4 Apprentices in all levels

2007 - 2012

Robert Bosch Pty Ltd, Melbourne, Australia

Production and test engineer

- Find root cause of production issues, implement actions to avoid re occurrences.
- New product introduction (NPI), production release of test stations and software.
- Improvement of final test equipment, cycle time and yield rate.
- Test and release of software for final testers in C.

2000 - 2006

Robert Bosch Germany and Australia

Project management and Software development engineer

- Project organisation
- Responsibility for software project budget and timing.
- Developed engine control software and series introduction for production for Projects of Holden and Suzuki in C and Assembler

1999 - 2000

Bosch Braking Systems Co. Ltd., Yokohama, Japan

Postgraduate Intern

- Developed automated tests for ABS control units
- Implemented software tools in C/C++ and Visual Basic.

Languages

- German, Native speaker
- English, Fluent in reading and writing
- Japanese, Conversational
- French, Conversational

Interests

- Trading and investing
- Japanese culture
- Electronic music
- Fittness
- Renewable energy, decarbonisation

Education and Qualification

2023

Academy of information technology/ Coder Academy

Higher education diploma of Information Technology

2023

UDACITY

Nanodegree in C/C++

2012

Holmesglen TAFE, Melbourne

Certificate IV in Electrical- Photovoltaic Systems

1996 - 1999

HSR or University of Applied Sciences Rapperswil/ Switzerland

Bsc in electrical and electronics engineering

References

Available on request